欢迎来到这个呃
welcome to part two of this uh creation
of a lower weight
使用 Koya SS GUI 创建更轻重量的第二部分所以在第一
uh using Koya SS GUI so in the first
部分我们去了并且我们
part we went and we collected a whole
从互联网上收集了一大堆图像我们
bunch of image from the internet and we
有点破坏它们因此他们从
sort of corrupt them and hence them from
分辨率的角度来增强
the resolution perspective to augment
分辨率，然后我们给
the resolution and then we
每张图片加上标题，
captioned each of the image
这样我们就有了一个正确的描述，
such that we have a proper description
这对
that's going to be important for the
知识的训练很重要，
training of the lore
所以现在我们可以
so now we're at the stage where we can
去实际配置呃实际的
go and actually configure uh the actual
Laura
参数和 训练并
parameters and for the training and
开始训练 这样我们就可以真正
start the training so we can actually
得到我们的模型
get our model
那么你如何
so how do you go about training Aurora
在 GUI 中很好地训练 Aurora 有几个
well within the GUI there's a couple of
选项卡 有 drain boot stream boot
tabs there's drain boot stream boot
Laura dream boot 文本版本
Laura dream boot textual version fine
微调和实用程序就像我们一直在
tuning and utilities like we've been in
我们实际上
the utility sections where we actually
为我们的图像做了深唇字幕的实用部分
did deep lip captioning for our image
有一大堆其他像 wd14
there's a whole bunch of other like wd14
字幕基本字幕还有
captioning basic captioning there's a
一大堆你可以通过 GUI 做的事情，
whole bunch of things you can do through
但它是一个关于
the GUI as well but it's a focused
如何做 Dreamboat
tutorial on how to do the Dreamboat
Laura 的重点教程 所以我们将坚持
Laura so we're going to stick with what
使用我们需要使用的东西，
we need to use
但欢迎您探索
but you're welcome to explore uh the
其他选项卡以及其他正确的东西所以
other tabs and what else right so let's
现在让我们进入 Dreamboat 的传说，这是
go to the Dreamboat lore now this is
我们将开始配置
where we're going to start to configure
我们的方式的地方 我们将实际进行 Laura
how we're going to actually do our Laura
培训，所以首先我们需要
training so first thing first we need to
指定我们将使用什么模型
specify what model we're going to
作为基础，因此您
leverage as the base so there's a couple
可以做几件事您可以使用
of things you can do you can either use
自定义模型，您可以在其中选择
a custom model that where you can pick
实际模型 为包含模型的扩散器
the actual model file out for diffuser
文件夹输出模型文件，如果
folder that contains the model if that's
在我们的案例中是这样的话，我们将
what you have in our case we're going to
坚持基本原则，我们将
stick to the basics we're going to go
使用稳定的扩散器版本 1.5，
with the stable diffusion version 1.5
这将是一个基于扩散器的
which is going to be a diffuser-based
模型 它将被使用，
model that it's going to be used and
显然这不是 V2 模型，
obviously this is not a V2 model and
也不是 v 参数化模型，
it's not a v parameterization model
因为这仅在
because this is only available when
您进行 V2 稳定扩散模型时可用，
you're doing a V2 stable diffusion model
因此如果我们添加 selected 例如只是
so if we add selected for example just
为了向您展示稳定扩散 2.1 基础
to show you a stable diffusion 2.1 base
现在这是一个 V2 模型，
now this is a V2 model and it's got like
如果我们选择
this stability AI now if we were to pick
一个
a
稳定的扩散 2.1，它是一个 v
stable diffusion 2.1 which is a v
参数化模型，那么它现在就像这个稳定性 AI，那么在这种情况下
parameterization model then in this case
它会自动被标记，但在
automatically it's getting tagged but in
我们的例子中我们想坚持使用基本的
our case we want to stick with the basic
稳定扩散 v1.5 所以我们要
stable diffusion with v1.5 so we're
退出，现在我们要将
going to quit that now we're going to
生成的 Laura 保存为安全
save the resulting Laura as a safe
张量文件格式，这样您
tensors file format so that's here you
就可以在这里选择其他文件格式，如果您
could select other file formats if you
想要扩散器模型 A 扩散器
wanted like a diffuser Model A diffuser
with safex with safe tensors
with safex with safe tensors files
里面的文件，但我们
inside but we're going to stick with
save tensors
现在要坚持在下一个选项卡中保存张量，我们将不得不
now in the next tab we're going to have
指定我们
to specify folders where we are going to
现在要保存我们信息的文件夹，如果你去
keep our information now if you go here
我们原来的呃
in our original uh
目录这里我们有詹妮弗
directory here we have the Jennifer
安妮斯顿 我们用 Laura
Aniston folder we created with the Laura
子文件夹和图像子文件夹创建的文件夹现在
sub folder and the image subfolder now
您不需要，这很棘手，您
you don't want and this is tricky you
不想选择 100 Jennifer
don't want to select the 100 Jennifer
Aniston 文件夹 Koya 有点，
Aniston folder Koya is a little bit
因为您可能有一大堆
because you could have a whole bunch of
不同的模型 你会
different models that you would train at
同时训练，这样你就可以拥有
the same time so you could have like a
第二个模型，因为我不认识
second model for I don't know
Phil Collins 或其他什么有洞察力的人，
Phil Collins or something else Insight
但在我们的例子中，我们将
here but in our case we're going to
与一个单一的模型进行交易，那就是
trade with a single model which is the
珍妮弗安妮斯顿，所以我 我只是
uh Jennifer Aniston so I'm just going to
去复制这个路径，就像
go and copy this path like the the
在斜杠 IMG 处停止的文件夹一样，所以
folder that stops at the slash IMG so
我要复制它，现在我
I'm going to copy that and now I'm going
要将它粘贴到图像
to go and paste this into the image
文件夹
folder
um
位置，这样就可以了 读取
location so this will go and read
其中 100 Jennifer Aniston 的子文件夹的内容，
the content of the subfolder inside
这
which is 100 Jennifer Aniston and this
将告诉 Koya SS 我们想
is going to tell Koya SS that we want to
在训练期间对每张图像重复 100 次，
do 100 repeats of every image during the
因此它将查看每张
training so it's going to look at every
图像 100 次，因此
image 100 times so that's about
我们需要大约 1600 步 将经历
1600 steps that we're gonna go through
Laura 的学习过程，
for the learning process of the Laura
所以
um
我们不需要 Laura 的正则化图像，
so regularization image we don't need
但它在那里你可以
that for Laura but it's there you could
使用它它有一些有趣的效果，
use it it's got some interesting effect
但我个人
but I don't personally use
在做 Laura 时不使用正则化图像
regularization image when I do a Laura
output 文件夹 我们要在哪里输出
output folder where do we want to Output
实际生成的图像 在我们的例子中
the actual resulting image in our case
我们要将它输出到 stable
we're going to Output that to the stable
diffusion web UI
文件夹 所以我要进入我的 stable
folder so I'm going to go into my stable
diffusion web UI 并且我们想在
diffusion web UI and we want to Output
embeddings 文件夹，所以
that under the embeddings folder so
我们要复制它，
we're going to go copy that
所以我要把它放在
so I'm gonna go and put that in the
embeddings 下一个是我们要去哪里，
embeddings next one is we're gonna where
我们想要
do we want the logs uh that are going to
在训练期间创建的日志，呃，
be created during the training where do
我们想要在哪里 将所有这些日志放入
we want to put all those logs so we're
going to put those into a subfolder
lower 文件夹下方的子文件夹中，因此
within the lower the lower folder so
我们将进入 Laura 反斜杠日志下方，
we're going to go under Laura backslash
logs
因此我将把日志放入该
so I'm going to put the logs in that
文件夹中我们想要什么 命名我们的模型
folder what do we want to name our model
默认情况下它被称为最后但在这种
by default it's called last but in this
情况下我将调用模型
case I'm going to call the model
来推断
to infer
旋转并且它将是一个版本
spun and it's going to be a version one
模型所以我将它命名为 v1.0
model so I'm going to name it v1.0 just
以便我知道什么时候我 查看模型
so that I know when I look at the model
名称，这是
name that this was the version one of
我们创建的模型的第一个版本，
the model that we created
do we want to add some training comments
在这种情况下，我们想添加一些训练评论吗？我真的不需要呃
in this case I don't really need to uh
训练参数，我们现在要去这里，
training parameters we're gonna go here
这是有趣的地方 东西从
now this is where the interesting stuff
这里开始，如果我们想
start so here it's if we want to start
从现有的劳拉开始训练，你
training from an existing Laura you
可以选择一个现有的文件，这样
could go and select an existing file so
你就可以继续训练，但
that you could keep training on it but
在我的情况下，我没有任何现有的
in my case I don't have any existing
劳拉文件可以开始，因为我们' 我
Laura file to start from because we're
要创建一个全新的，所以我
going to create a brand new one so I
将它留空 training batch size
leave it empty training batch size what
我发现效果很好的实际上是将
I find works well is actually to set the
训练 batch size 设置为两个
training batch size to two number of
epoch 我只想做一个我想
epoch I only want to do one I want to
在每个 Epoch 保存现在显然
save at every Epoch obviously now the
caption extension that's important to
设置的字幕扩展很重要，所以它是鸭子 txt 字幕，因为
set so it's a duck txt caption because
这是我们
this is the captioning extension that we
在使用实际
have created when we use the actual
实用程序时创建的字幕扩展，您将在此处看到我们
utilities you're gonna see here that we
使用 txt 的字幕文件扩展名，
use the caption file extension of the
因此我们想使用
txt so we want to use the same caption
标题字段中的相同标题扩展混合
extension here in the caption field
精度我倾向于使用 FP 或 bf16，
mixed Precision I tend to use FP or bf16
因为它提供更好的精度，它
because it gives better Precision it's
几乎像浮点级别，但
almost like floating Point level but at
实际内存占用量的一半，
half the actual memory footprint and
当我保存我的模型时，我将它们和
when I save my model I save them as well
bf16 一起保存，具体取决于 你
as bf16 depending on the card that you
有 Nvidia 卡的卡你可能会或可能
have the Nvidia card you may or may not
不会使用 bf16 但对我来说因为我的
be able to use bf16 but for me since my
卡支持它是一个更好的选择呃
card supported it's a better option uh
喜剧每个内核的 CPU Treads
comedy a number of CPU Treads per core
保持在一到两个之间就像我的
keep it between one and two it's like my
CPU 有两个 每个核心线程，所以我将
CPU has two thread per core so I'm going
它保留为 2
to leave it as two the seed random
你可以选择的种子随机数 我将它保留为
number that you can pick I leave it to
1 二 3 4 但你可以更改
one two three four but you can change it
它 没关系 这取决于你 但我
it doesn't matter it's up to you but I
保留 我喜欢保留它 因为
keep I like keeping it because then for
如果我重建模型
repeatability if I rebuild the model
然后为了可重复性我知道它将开始使用
then I know it's going to start using
相同的种子所以我应该期望
the same seed so I should expect
使用与
Improvement using the same kind of
原始模型中使用的相同类型的种子进行改进
seed that was used in the original one
所以我想保留它让我们看一组
so I'd like to keep that let's see a set
point burning rate 什么是
point burning rate what is a good
较低模型的良好学习率
learning rate for a lower model
通常学习率
typically learning rate of
0.0001 是好的，就像我
0.0001 is good just as the as the base I
喜欢训练我的低运行模型的基础一样，呃，
like to train my low run models uh
constant
没有预热的恒定水平，
levels with no warm-ups
所以学习率为零的恒定调度程序
so constant scheduler for learning rate
预热百分比 嗯，我们想要
with zero percent warm-ups uh we want to
缓存潜伏，以便更快地
Cache the latent so that it's faster to
训练文本编码器学习率，将
train text encoder learning rate it's
其保持在 5e 减 5 作为
good to keep it to 5e Minus 5 as the
实际学习率是很好的，显然对于
actual learning rate and obviously for
单位学习率 1 e 减 3
the unit learning rate one e minus three
也不错 从字面上看，
is not a bad place to start so literally
我也可以将其设置为 1 e 减
I could set that as well to one e minus
3，就像理论上一样，因为如果您
three like in theory because if you set
同时设置这两个值，那么
both of those this value is ignored by
如果您没有设置任何一个，培训师将忽略该值，
the trainer if you didn't set any of
并且该值
those and this value would take would
实际上是 适用于两者所以我喜欢
actually be be applied to both so I like
以较低的学习率训练我的文本编码器
to train my text encoder at the lower
然后我将训练
learning rate then I'm going to train
the unit
网络等级的单位数量呃将它推到
number of network ranks uh push it up to
128 和网络 Alpha 个人我
128 and the network Alpha personally I
发现它最好在 128 所以 匹配
find it to be best at 128 so matching
顶部，所以如果我确实喜欢 64 等级的劳拉，
the top so if I did like a 64 rank Laura
我会将网络 Alpha 保持为 64。
I would keep the network Alpha to be 64.
但由于我正在做 128，我将把
but since I'm doing a 128 I'm going to
它保持在 128。最大分辨率年 512
keep it to 128. max resolution year 512
又是 512，所以它会继续 以在 512 乘以 512 的像素数内适应所有
by 512 again so it's going to fit all of
这些不同纵横比的图像。
those different aspect ratio image
within the pixel count of 512 times 512.
所以它不会比那个更高，
so it's not going to go higher than that
所以它将把它限制在
so it's going to keep it confined within
最大分辨率尺寸内
that maximum resolution size
停止训练编码器所以我们
uh stop training encoder so we're not
不会 做到这一点，呃，启用桶，这
going to do that uh enable buckets this
就是让你能够使用
is what gives you the ability to use
各种纵横比图像的原因，所以你想
various aspect ratio image so you want
保留那个打勾的
to leave that ticked
高级配置，我们
Advanced configuration we're going to
需要去设置一些
need to go and set a few things token
我们不改变梯度
padding we don't change that gradient
累积的东西令牌填充 我们不使用任何
accumulation we don't use any of that
先前丢失的重量，我们将它留给一个
prior lost weight we leave it to one
我们将做一个
we're gonna do a
8 位原子并使用
8-bit atoms and use x formers the
默认的 x 形式，所以保持这样我们不会
default so keep that like that we're not
做颜色或翻转增强
going to do color nor flip augmentation
我们' 我将使用跳过剪辑 2。我发现
we're going to use skip clip 2. I find
当你跳过两个剪辑时，这会提供更好的结果，
that this provides better results when
you when you do a clip skip of two
我们不想使用内存高效
uh we don't want to use memory efficient
注意力，因为我的卡足够大，
attention because my card is big enough
可以毫无问题地实际运行它
to actually run that without any issue
所以 我将保持关闭状态，因为
so I'm going to keep that off because
这会使训练变慢，但随后
this would make training slower but then
它会减少你的呃 Nvidia 卡上的 vram 使用率
it reduced the vram usage on your uh
呃这里我不关心在
Nvidia cards uh here I don't care about
我完成这里的训练时保存训练状态
saving the training State when I'm done
我可以指定
with the training here I could specify
如果我有一个安全的训练状态，我可以
if I had a safe training State I could
指定训练状态文件夹以
specify the training State folder to
从中恢复训练，以及
resume training from it and the maximum
number of epoch
我不需要更改的最大纪元数，我将
I don't really need to change that I'm
让系统
going to let the system specify it
通过计算指定它和最大值 每个
through the calculation and the maximum
数据加载器的工作人员数量我喜欢
number of workers per data loader I like
把它设置为一个，它会让事情更快地
to put that to one it make things faster
开始训练，如果你
to actually start uh the training if you
把它放在一个工具上，那么
put that to a tool to high number then
it may actually end up being slower to
start training
当你完成时，它实际上可能会更慢地开始训练 我喜欢
when you're done with that what I like
做的是我喜欢去保存我的
to do is I like to go and save my
配置文件，这样我就不会丢失
configuration file so that I don't lose
用于
the parameters that were used for the
培训课程的参数所以我倾向于做的是
training session so what I tend to do is
我进入我的 Laura 文件夹我只是
I go into my Laura folders I'm just
去 去复制这个快速入门
going to go and copy this quick start
Laura for Jennifer Aniston 我只是要用
Laura for Jennifer Aniston and I'm just
反斜杠出去 我将
going to go out on a backslash I'm going
调用它 v1.0.json
to call that v1.0.json
这样我们将创建一个 Json
so that we're going to create a Json
文件这是格式 对于
file which is the format for the
配置文件，我们将把
configuration file and we're going to
它保存为 v1.0，最终与
save it as a v1.0 that ends up matching
v1.0 模型输出名称匹配，所以现在
the v1.0 model output name so now
有一个相关性，所以
there's a correlation so it's easier
在路上更容易找到
down the road to go and find that the
你没有的工具选项卡
tools tab you don't really need those
如果您想像
are tools if you wanted to prepare like
梦想中的靴子一样准备，我们真的不需要这些工具，在这种情况下我们已经手动完成了，
your dream boot we've done it manually
但是有一种方法可以
in this case but there is a way to kind
加载任何
of load any
文件夹，包括包含图像的文件夹
folders including that includes image
，然后您可以指定重复次数，
and then you can specify your repeats
这有点像 为您构建一个结构，
and it kind of builds a structure for
我们在这里手动完成，所以
you we've done it manually here so don't
不需要这样做还有像
need to do that there's also like
Dreamboat Laura 数据集平衡，
Dreamboat Laura data set balancing that
您可以这样做，您可以使用合并 Laura 和
you can do there's a merge Laura and a
验证 Laura 工具，所以
verify Laura tool that you can use so
您可以使用其他工具
other tools you can go and sort of play
如果你有兴趣，就去玩吧，但我们
with if you are interested but we don't
不需要将它们作为本次
need to use those as part of this
培训课程的一部分，
training session
所以我认为我们
so I think we're pretty good to start uh
现在可以开始了，嗯，所以我们要开始
at this point so we're gonna go and
培训了，嗯 很快，在
start the training uh pretty soon
我们开始训练之前，
just one quick thing before we start the
我想仔细检查一下我
training I want to double check with my
以前的 Cyndi
previous training parameters for a Cyndi
Lauper 模型的训练参数，我只是想
Lauper model I did just want to make
确保我有正确的单位，所以
sure that I've got the right unit uh so
在这里查看我的学习率是什么
see my learning rate here for what zero
零零一这样我们就可以看到
zero one so that would well let's see
零零点零零零一
about zero zero dot zero zero zero one
所以这就是我要设置的位置
so that's what I'm going to set it at
然后让我们仔细检查下一个
and let's double check the next one
是呃
which was uh
预热零所以我使用
warm up zero so I was using with
常量很好呃 BF 16，所以我只想
constant that's fine uh BF 16 so I just
检查单元学习
want to check okay the unit learning
率，它前面是三个零，
rate which was three zero in front of
所以让我们确保我在这里削减了
the one so let's make sure I've cut the
完全相同的
exact same
配置，因为我不想
configuration here because I don't want
to
得到坏模型，因为我做了 一个
get with the bad model because I did a
错误的配置 其他一切都应该
wrong config everything else should be
很好
fine
名称 其他一切都很好 所以我认为
name everything else is good so I think
我们现在可以开始了 所以让我们保存你这样
we're good to go now so let's save so
做的方式 现在你一旦
the way you do that so now you once
你得到了我们要去的呃配置文件名
you've got like the uh config file name
单击“保存”，这
we're going to click on Save and this is
将把它保存在我们的
going to go and save this within our
文件夹中，所以如果我们去检查文件夹，嗯，
folder so if we go and check the folder
你会看到 Jennifer
um here you're going to see Jennifer
Aniston Laura 和 winter 应该是
Aniston Laura and winter should be the
v1.0 文件，如果我们双击
v1.0 file and if we double click on that
这是
this is the actual config that is for
Jennifer Aniston 模型的实际配置，
the Jennifer Aniston model and
如您所见，批量大小
everything as you can see batch size
Epoch 的所有内容都与
Epoch everything is matching similar to
Cyndi Lauper 类型的模块相似，
what was for Cyndi Lauper type of module
好吧，现在我们已经
okay so now that this is there we're
准备好开始了 训练和
pretty much ready to start training and
开始训练就像
to start the training it's as easy as
点击训练模型一样简单
clicking on train model
现在你会看到它开始
and now you're gonna see that it starts
训练现在它吐出整个
the training now it spits out the whole
命令实际上将被提供
command that is actually going to be fed
给 CLI
to the CLI
以实际开始训练所以 你
to actually start the training so as you
可以在这里看到，所以现在你可以看到它，它
can see here so now you can see it it
查看了分桶，它发现
looked at the bucketing and it found
我们有 100 次重复的图像，这些图像
that we have 100 repeats of image that
将在 320 x 704 范围内，
are going to be in the 320 by 704 range
在其他分辨率下为 700，所以它会
700 in that other resolution so it kind
分桶所有不同的 图像
of buckets all of the different image
是每个桶中 16s 的一部分，
that are part of the 16s in each of
并
those buckets and kind of apply the
在这些桶上应用重复计数，所以我们将
repeat counts on those so we're gonna
得到一个总数，如果我们要将这个
get to a total if we were to Total this
加起来，它应该是 1600 呃总重复
up it should be 1600 uh total repeats
现在它有点通过
now it's kind of going through the
加载实际模型的过程，
process of loading the actual model and
然后加载图像，嗯，
then it's loading the image and the uh
所以它被删除了缓存，所以它加载了
so it's caching deleted so it's loading
所有不同的图像，并
all of the different image and created
从中创建和创建潜在模型，现在
and creating latents out of them and now
就像那样，它已经开始
just like that it's already starting to
训练模型了，嗯， 正如你所看到的，我们
train the model uh and as you can see we
现在有 800 次重复，你会想
have 800 repeats now you're going to
知道为什么你告诉我 800 会
wonder why 800 you told me it's going to
变成 1600，这是正确的，因为它是
be 1600 which is right because it's the
图像的总数，所以我们有 1600 个
total number of image so we have 1 600
经过训练的重复图像，现在我们
trained image with repeating now we have
设置了两个
set a two train
um
正确地训练 um 正确的措辞是
like the right the right wording is to a
训练批量大小为 2 所以因为我们的
train batch size of two so because we
批量大小为 2 我们实际上是
have a batch size of two we are
essentially training two image in
在 GPU 的内存中并行训练两个图像因此
parallel within the uh memory of the GPU
我们将 1 600
so because of that we're dividing 1 600
by 2 这给了我们 800 次重复，但它
by 2 which gives us 800 repeats but it's
仍然在做 1600 次，但是因为我们
still doing the 1600 but because we're
一次做两次，所以它减少了
doing two at a time it cuts down uh the
步数，两次达到 800 次。
number of steps and two to go to 800.
现在
now
你会问我为什么不这样做 想像
you're going to ask why wouldn't I want
to go and put like
16 那样放。呃训练过的批量大小
16. uh trained batch size
我想如果你有一个 vram 你
I guess if you're having a vram you
可以在你的 GPU 中做到这一点但
could do that in your GPU but the
问题是现在你将有很少的
problem is now you're gonna have so few
步骤就像你学习时
steps like when you learn
如果你看这个 这里的损失数字会
if you look at this loss number here
逐渐下降，
it's gradually going to go down right
但系统需要一段时间才能
but it takes a while for the system to
开始学习东西，如果你同时向它提供
start to learn things and if you feed it
太多信息来
too much information at once in parallel
并行训练，那么你最终的
to train then you end up having too few
步骤太少而且它不会 有足够的时间来
steps and it doesn't have enough time to
正确地学习模型，所以你
properly learn the model so you're
最好做一两个训练的批量大小，
better off to do trained batch size of
除非
one or two unless you have like maybe a
你的数据集中可能有几百张
couple hundred image in your data set
你想要交易的图像，然后
that you want to trade on and then it
在这一点上有意义 可能会有
makes sense at that point to maybe have
更大的批量大小，因为你
more a larger batch size because you're
要训练更多的
going to train over a longer number of
步骤，但在我们的例子中，因为我们只
steps but in our case because we're only
使用 16 张图像，我不想训练得
using 16 image I don't want to train too
太快，我希望系统需要一段时间
fast I want the system to take a while
训练需要一段时间，这样
the training to take a while such that
它就有机会
it gives a chance to learn the model
更好地学习模型，并随着时间的推移降低损失，
better and to get the loss to be lower
这样我们就开始
over time such that we start to learn
越来越多地了解模型，
more and more and more about the model
所以人们犯的一个错误是
so that's one mistake people make is
他们会 以太大的批次
they will train with too high a batch
大小进行训练，最终会限制
size and it's going to end up limiting
您可以在实际模型上进行的学习量，
the amount of learning you can do on an
actual model
所以我会在这里暂停，让
so I will pause here and I will let the
实际训练继续进行，一旦
actual training proceed and then once
完成，我们可以做几个
it's done uh we can do a couple of
提示查询模型并查看
prompt queries on the model and see the
结果
results
我们的模型现在已经准备好了，
our model is now ready
所以我猜我们损失了一个
so we have I guess gone to a loss of one
0.111，看起来还不错，最后一个会
0.111 and it looks okay the last will
因模型而异，但听起来
vary from model to model but that sounds
相当不错，
like fairly good
所以现在是时候开始了 并尝试这个
so now it's time to go and try this
名为 Jennifer Aniston
model which is called Jennifer Aniston
v1.0 safe dancer 的模型，让我们来看看
v1.0 safe dancer so let's go and have a
它
look at that
好吧，让我们转到稳定的扩散 Web
okay so let's go to stable diffusion web
UI，
UI
在这里我们要加载确保
and here we're going to load make sure
我们加载了 prune 模型
that we have the prune model
v15 作为一个检查点，
v15 loaded as a checkpoint and
不需要像
don't really need like to change like
大多数人那样改变它会成为一个
for most people it's going to be an
自动
automatic
vae，所以我喜欢像这样使用 VA ft MSC
vae so I like to use the VA ft MSC in
like this one
作为我的 VA
as my VA
现在我们需要去加载一些并
now we need to go and load some and
配置它 这样我们就可以使用
configure this so that we can use
自动或自动一对一，所以有
automatic or Auto one one one so there's
两种方法可以做到，你可以
two ways you can do that you can either
使用称为 SD web
use an extension uh that's called SD web
UI 附加网络的扩展来实际加载
UI additional networks to actually load
它们，这是由 koi ISS 制作的，或者你可以
them which is made by koi ISS or you can
使用内置的 - 在
use the built-in
Auto one one one Laura uh
Auto one one one one Laura uh
embedding settings 如果你点击
embedding settings if you click on that
这里的那个小图标 show Extra Networks
little icon here show Extra Networks
你会看到文本反转
you're going to see textual inversion
超网络和 Laura 所以如果我在
hyper networks and Laura so if I go
Laura 下我们会看到我们
under Laura we're going to see that we
有我们的 Jennifer  Aniston V1 顺便说一下，
have our Jennifer Aniston V1 and by the
我犯了一个错误，就像我在
way I made it a mistake like when I
配置和这里我的文件夹时使用了
configured and here my folders I use the
嵌入目标，这是错误的，
embeddings destination which was wrong
我应该使用默认的
right I should have used the default
Laura
文件夹，所以它应该是
folder within so it should have been
这个文件夹，所以如果我去这里 而
this one instead so if I go here instead
不是嵌入我应该
of embeddings I should have used this
在模型下使用它我应该使用
under models I should have used the
模型文件夹本身中的 Laura 文件夹
Laura folder within the models folder
作为我的目的地所以我
itself for my destination so what I've
现在所做的是我将生成的
done now is I kind of move the resulting
文件移动到该文件夹​​中
file into that folder
以便我们拥有它所以我 我将把
so that we have that so I'm going to
它保存为默认值，所以这是
save it as the as the default so this is
你放置你的
where you would put your
uh
文件的地方，我猜你的文件还有其他
I guess your your file there's other
方法你也可以配置，比如如果你
ways you can also configure like if you
使用扩展名，例如
use the extension for example
um
在这里你将找到的设置
here under settings you're going to find
就像一个额外的网络
like an additional networks
配置选项卡，您可以在其中指定
configuration tab where you can specify
其他位置，您可以在其中存储
other location where you might store
一些 lauras，这是另一种
some of your lauras so that's another
访问方式，但
way to kind of access that but by
默认情况下，在 Auto 中，Laura
default in Auto one one one that Laura
文件夹是所有实际 Lora
folder is where all of the actual Lora
模型所在的位置 放这样你就可以
models should be put so that you can
使用它们
make use of them
所以我们将使用自动 1111
so we're going to use the auto 1111
方法来实际使用 dolora
method to actually make use of dolora
所以第一件事我会去尝试获得
so first thing I'll go and try to get
我做过一段时间的现有提示之一
one of the existing prompt that I did a
就像呃当 在与 Laura 合作时，
while like uh when when working with
我们可以将其重新用作
Laura's so we can reuse that as a
我们将
template for the prompt that we're going
用于生成图片的提示的模板，
to use to generate the pictures
呃，所以我将进入稳定扩散的输出
uh so I'm going to go under outputs of
stable diffusion
，在这里我将进入我的形象
and here I'm going to go under my image
文件夹，我会找到一张
folder and I'm going to find like an
我过去生成的
image that I've generated in the past
看起来不错的图像，所以假设我们
that looks good so let's say that we
喜欢这个风格，我们
like the style of this one and we would
希望看到 Jennifer
like to see our picture of Jennifer
Aniston 的一般风格照片
Aniston in the general style that this
图片提供了，所以我们要去这里
picture provides so we're gonna go here
，我要去把它拖到
and I'm gonna go and drag this into
这个呃字段中，它会吐出
this uh field and it spits out all of
这张图片中的所有元数据信息，
the metadata info that were within this
现在我可以使用这个图标将
image and now I can use this icon to
配置推送到哪里 它需要
kind of push the config where it needs
在提示负舞会
to be in the prompt the negative prom
字段中，其他所有内容都按照
field and everything else gets kind of
我
configured the way it was when I
生成此图片时的方式进行配置，我
generated this picture one thing that I
要确保禁用的一件事是我
will want to make sure I disable is I
不想启用实际的
don't want to enable the actual
附加网络 因为我用它
additional networks because I used that
来创建图像 我想向您展示
to create the image I want to show you
如何使用自动一对一
how to use the auto one one one
内置的 Lora 支持，这样您就不必
built-in Lora support so you don't have
安装额外的扩展来
to install that extra extension to
生成您的图像，所以现在我们有
generate your image so now that we have
正确的设置 只是为了
the right settings in place just for the
好玩，让我们禁用高风险
fun let's I'm going to disable high-risk
修复，因为它需要一段时间
fix because it's going to take a while
才能生成，但让我们生成这种
to generate but let's generate the kind
图片，这将
of picture this would this would produce
在没有
on its own without any uh
任何劳拉的情况下自行生成，所以你可以 看到
any Laura so you can kind of see the
图片的风格还不错我的意思是
style of picture it's not bad I mean
这不是一张糟糕的图片它是默认的
it's not a bad picture it's a default
稳定扩散 1.5 类型图像但是如果
stable diffusion 1.5 Type image but if
我们开始添加我们的 Laura 所以我将
we start to add our Laura so I'm going
在此处进入该提示并且我
to go into that prompt here and I'm
将扩展 额外的网络，
going to expand the additional Network
我要点击这个 Jennifer
and I'm going to click on this Jennifer
Aniston V1 模型，
Aniston V1 model
现在你会看到它
now you're gonna see that it added this
在 The Prompt 的末尾添加了这个所以我想
at the end of The Prompt so I want to
移动它所以 Ctrl X 我想把
move this so Ctrl X and I want to move
它移到开头 因为这
it up to the beginning because this is
很好，我想在
well I guess it doesn't matter in the
劳拉的情况下没关系，它可能在最后它
case of a Laura it can be at the end it
没有任何它不是一个令牌它
doesn't have any it's not a token it's
只是一个
just going to be an embedding that's
将要被替换的嵌入所以我们要
going to be replaced so we're going to
坚持你可能想做的一件事
stick with that one thing you may want
是，我认为如果你将
to do is I think if you lower the
这个较低的强度降低到 0.7，
strength of this lower to 0.7
效果会更好，我们将尝试
it's a better effect we're going to try
0.7 和 1，这是 allora 的默认值，
at 0.7 and 1 which is the default for
当你实际将它添加到
allora when you actually add it to the
提示 呃 但我们要使用 0.7
prompt uh but we're going to go with 0.7
因为我知道通常这会
because I know usually this tend to
产生更好的图像 我们要
produce better image and we're going to
添加
add the
um 标题中的一些词
um some of the words from the caption
这基本上我们要将
which essentially we're gonna add
Jennifer
Aniston 添加
Aniston
到提示 我们已经有了
to the prompt and we already have the
关键字 woman，它已经是其中的一部分
keyword woman which is already part of
我们将确保提示有意义
this we're going to make sure that the
我认为它
prompt kind of makes sense I think it
确实 Jennifer 有一种褐色的空气
does Jennifer has sort of brownish air
所以我们应该没问题 如此迷人的年轻
so we should be fine so attractive young
女性 美丽的脸庞 详细的眼睛
woman beautiful face detailed eyes
烟熏眼妆所以波浪形的头发
smokey eye makeup so wavy hair that's
没关系所以我认为我们很好地进行
all right so I think we're good to give
测试所以让我们关闭它我们
it a test so let's close that and we're
将制作一批四张所以我们
gonna make a batch of four so we're
将获得四张图片而不是一张
gonna get four image instead of just one
我们 将获得四张图像
we're gonna get four images
渲染
render
所以让我们去看看它给我们带来了什么
so let's go and let's see what it gives
结果
us a result
所以我们已经可以看到詹妮弗安妮斯顿
so we can already see Jennifer Aniston
成为渲染的一部分
being part of the render
并且哇，如果我
and wow that looks pretty solid if I'm
问我认为我们有一个非常可靠的
asking I think we have a pretty solid
渲染
render
并且我 认为这些图像变得
and I think those image are turning to
非常好
be pretty good
所以如果我单击它让我们在
so if I click on it let's look at one in
the
展开的视图中看一个美丽的我认为这正是
expanded view beautiful I think this is
pretty
我们所期望的
exactly what we are would expect
眼睛可能有点
eyes might be a little bit
糟糕但我认为这还不错我的意思是 我们
bad but I think it's not bad I mean we
有一个非常好的图像，我会给你一个技巧，
have a pretty good image one trick I'm
gonna give you
这些图像看起来不错，但要
those image looks good but there is to
改进这些图像，你可以做的
improve on those image what you can do
是，你实际上可以打开
is you can actually turn on
呃高分辨率修复它要做的
uh high-res fix what that's going to do
是它会
is it's going to scale up this image to
在这种情况下，将此图像放大到大小的 1.5 倍，这样
in this case 1.5 times the size so that
它就不是 384 x 704，而是
it is instead of being 384 by 704 it's
576 x 1056，但它
going to be 576 by 1056 but it does it
使用潜在的
using the latent
um 图像来实现它，因此它缩放潜在的而
um image so it scales the latent instead
不是仅仅做一个 upres 产生
of just doing an upres which produce
更好的结果并且当你这样做时它产生了
much better results and It produced much
看起来更自然的呃结果
more natural looking uh results when you
所以让我们再次运行它
do that so let's run it again
现在需要更多时间因为
it's going to take more time now because
我们将不得不提升实际
we're gonna have to upres the actual
图像所以它做的第一件事就是
image so the first thing it does and
生成准确的图像 我们添加
generates the exact same image we add uh
在上一次运行中生成的相同图像，但是当
generated in the previous run but when
它达到 50% 时，它将
it gets to 50 percent then it's going to
开始升级和
start to upscale and
分组并创建
group and create high resolution
这些图像的高分辨率版本，看起来会
versions of those image which will look
好得多，
much better
所以现在你会看到它们
so now you are going to see that they
会变成 软，
will become soft
因为现在他们有点像它正在
because now they have been kind of it's
使用它在低分辨率下所做的最终图像的潜在版本
using the latent version of the final
来开始
image it did at low resolution to start
创建高共振的过程
the process of creating a high resonage
这样做是为了确保
what that does is that it ensures
一致性它不会创建一个
consistency it's not going to create one
关键图像因为它有 分辨率太高 请
key image because it's got too high a
记住，该模型是
resolution remember that this model was
在 512 x 512 分辨率上训练的，
trained on a 512 by 512 resolution
因此如果您尝试生成
so if you try to produce image that are
远高于此分辨率的图像，它往往会
well Above This resolution it tends to
创建可怕的图像，但通过利用
create monstrous image but by leveraging
这种潜在的放大，它将保持
this latent upscaling it will keep the
最终生成的外观 图像，它
look of the final produced image and it
会知道头部、
will know where the head and the
肩膀和腿应该在哪里，
shoulders and the legs should be and
然后它会使用它以适当连贯的方式创建
then it will just use that to create the
精细范围的渲染
render of the fine range
in a properly
所以现在如果我们看
coherent matter so now if we look at
那些我们可以看到现在我们有 更精细的
those we can see that now we have finer
细节你已经可以看到
details you can already see that the
图片看起来
pictures look
更清晰你可以看到
a lot more defined you can see the
背景模糊它看起来
background the blurriness it looks
很棒岩石
awesome the Rocks
它是一个完美的图像让我们尝试
it's a perfect image let's try another
另一个只是为了踢一下我们去从
one just for a kick let's go and pick
一堆中挑选另一个呃让我们
another one out of the bunch uh let's go
回到最近的一个，例如我为
back to a more recent one for example I
did a couple of share the model for
Cyndi Lauper 做了几个分享模型让我们试试我不知道
Cyndi Lauper let's try I don't know if
这是否会运作良好，因为那是
that's going to work well because that's
一个非常疯狂的图像，但让我们说如果我们
a pretty crazy image but let's say if we
要在什么地方重用这个提示 我们
were to reuse this prompt where we're
要求紫色或粉红色和红色的
asking for purple or for pink and red
头发 我不知道这是否适用于
hair I don't know if that would work on
我们的模型 尝试很有趣 让我们
our model it's interesting to try let's
疯狂地尝试一下 所以我们将
go wild and try that so we're going to
应用与我相同的设置 但现在
apply the same settings I had but now
我' 我要回去把我们的
I'm going to go back and bring back our
詹妮弗·安妮斯顿带回来，
Jennifer Aniston
我们将用詹妮弗·安妮斯顿 1990 年代 1990 年代的衣服取代 1980 年代的辛迪·劳珀，
and we're going to replace Cyndi Lauper
1980s with Jennifer Aniston 1990s
所以这会给
1990d so it's so it's going to tend to
她带来 1990 年代风格的服装，我
give her a clothing of 1990 style and I
想其他一切都应该在照片上
guess everything else should be photo
很有吸引力 好吧，嘴唇
attractive okay lips
有翅膀的眼线紧身体粉红色的头发所以
winged eye line tight body pink hair so
我们要求粉红色的头发所以让我们
it's we're asking for pink hair so let's
看看我们穿了一件夹克是什么让我们
see what we get wearing a jacket uh yeah
试一试好奇看看
let's give it a try curious to see what
这会给我们带来什么
that's going to give us
不应该理论很好
shouldn't Theory be pretty good
劳拉很好地解决了
that Laura is complying quite well to
你给它的问题，就像
the problem that you are giving it like
她有夹克，她有
it's she's got the jacket she's got like
粉红色的空气，
the pink Air
你真的可以看到这是她
you can really see that it's her
和歌剧，所以我认为我们学到的
and the operas so I think we've learned
可能有点太多了
maybe a little bit too much like the
模型在创建输出时
model when it when it creates the output
它非常强大正确对比度
it's pretty strong right the contrast is
非常高就像高分辨率修复一样
very high like the high-res fix kind of
使它恢复到更自然的色调
brings it back to a more natural tone
但这告诉我的是
but what that tells me is
我可能应该减少是的看到我
I should probably reduce yeah see I I
有价值 在这种情况下为 1，
had the value to one in this case
而不是 0.7，这就是为什么它如此
instead of 0.7 this is why it was so
强大，所以
strong so to kind of tone it down a
如果你将
little bit if you bring the actual
模型的实际重量 uh 调整为 0.7，那么它会稍微调低一点，然后它会
weight of the model uh to 0.7 then it
产生一个对比度较低的基础
kind of produce a less contrasty base
图像，即
image which is
更多 看起来很自然，我想当你
more natural looking I guess when you
这样做的时候，但即使从
when you do that but still even starting
一个非常反差的图像开始，它
it with a very contrasty image it's
也会产生非常好的
going to produce very good
结果，
results
让我们等待最终的渲染，
let's wait for the final render
你已经有了它，所以现在我们有一个
there you have it so now we have a
非常好的詹妮弗安妮斯顿图像，我的意思是
Jennifer Aniston image very good I mean
那些 没有像它们那样被挑选它们
those are not picked like they're they
实际上就像是从稳定的
are literally like out of a stable
扩散中出来的没有没有挑剔
diffusion no no pickiness like that the
通过这个模型产生的图片
the picture produced through this model
大多是 100 好和可用
are mostly 100 good and usable very
很少需要做修饰它们
little needs to be done to retouch them
即使衣服有点在
even the clothing is kind of in the
1990 年代的风格有点
1990s style like it's this one is kind
糟糕，我猜是黑眼睛，
of a little bit bad I guess dark eyes
因为我们有一个非常对比的开始，
because we had a very contrasty start
但只是为了向你展示不同之处，我
but just to show you the difference I'm
不会做高的休息，
not going to do the high of the up rest
但如果我去和 降低这个值让我们说
but if I go and lower this to let's say
0.5 甚至比 0.7 低得多，并
0.5 even much lower than 0.7 and
重新生成图像，它们不会得到
regenerate the image they will not get
那么高的对比度，因为现在我们施加
as contrasty because now we're applying
less weight now it's quite possible that
的重量更少了，面部特征很可能不像
the feature of the face will be less
Jennifer Aniston，因为我们的
like Jennifer Aniston because we have
重量更轻 但考虑到
less weight but given the strong model
我们在开始时添加的强大模型存在，我认为这
presence that we add to start I think it
会很好
will be fine
，给她一个相当明确的
and giving her a fairly well-defined
脸
face
，然后你就可以了，所以我们的
and there you go so we have a much
低音图像对比度要低得多，
less contrasty bass image
所以你可以根据
uh so you can play with those values to
自己的喜好使用这些值 并且有点改变
your taste and kind of change the
图像的整体外观和感觉而
overall look and feel of the image
不是粉红色的头发我们可以只是
instead of pink hair we could just take
为了好玩而把它拿出来
that out for example just for a just for
并坚持
fun and stick out the
头发颜色的规范现在它
specification for hair color and now it
应该在这里生成我们的自然头发
should generate with our natural hair
颜色
color
我们 去吧，现在我们有了一个
here we go so now we have like a version
带有她自然发色的图像版本，
of the image with her natural hair
color
所以我希望这能为您提供一个
so I hope this is giving you kind of a
良好的基础，让您开始创建
good base to get going with creating
自己的 Laura 并创建像好
your own Laura and creating good picture
照片一样的好照片也需要一个好的
like a good picture also require a good
提示
prompt
嗯 我发现你可以使用的一件事，
um one thing I've found to you can use
也许我会向你展示这个
and maybe I'm going to show you this
技巧，这些年我正在使用 Chad GPT
trick years I'm kind of using Chad GPT
来帮助创建一些舞会，
to help with some of those prom
creations
嗯，
um
我将向你展示它是什么
I'm going to show you one how what it
看起来如果我去打开我的聊天
looks like if I go and open up my chat
GPT 你的会话已经过期了
GPT your session has expired
呃好吧让我们暂时忘记它我
uh well let's forget about it for now I
想我可以制作一个单独的视频来说明
guess I can make a separate video on how
如何做到这一点但是是的
to do that but yeah
嗯
um
这远远超出了
that's going well beyond the scope of
这个视频的范围所以改为 跳入
this video so instead of jumping into
其中并使这种方式太长让我们
that and making this way too long let's
暂时保持它，我将在
keep it to that for now and I'm gonna
磁盘中添加到
add into the disk into the description
YouTube 视频的描述中，例如指向
of the YouTube video like links to the
扩展文件夹的链接，
extension folder uh the extension that
如果你想要的话，你需要安装的扩展 要使用
you need to install if you want to use
这个额外的网络，请看这里这是
this additional Network see here this is
制作劳拉的另一种方法，如果我从这里
the other way to do a Laura if I take
拿出来，
this out
from here
显然现在如果我渲染这个，我们
obviously now if I render this we're
将得到
gonna get
一些基本的东西，
something basic that is not going to
看起来不会很像詹妮弗安妮斯顿，
look very much like Jennifer Aniston it
有点像 看起来像 ER 但它不如
kind of looks like ER but it's not as
我们使用 Lora um 时得到的那么好
good as what we get when we use the Lora
um
所以这可能是
so this is probably one of the reason
我们拥有如此强大的背景或
why we have such a strong background or
强大的 Vibe 的原因之一因为我们已经对
a strong Vibe because we already have
她有了相当多的了解
like quite a bit of knowledge about her
扩散已经稳定了，呃，
in stable diffusion already uh
但是如果我加入这个 Jennifer Aniston，
but if I kick in this Jennifer Aniston
然后我把它踢回去，让我们说这里的
and I kick it back to let's say 0.7 here
权重为 0.7，
from the weight
然后重新生成图像，现在我们
and regenerate the image now we're going
要让 Laura 实际重新
to get the Laura to actually
创建它，它应该是
recreate it it should be it should be
一样的 像我们以前的图像，
the same image as we had before
这就是你如何使用这个
and that's how you can use this
额外的网络，它可能更
additional Network which might be more
方便，因为它使你能够将
convenient because it gives you the
一堆 loras 堆叠
ability to stack also a bunch of loras
在一起，每个具有
on one on top of each others with
不同的权重，所以你可以最终得到
different weights so you can end up with
uh
I 当你创建你的图像时猜测 loras 的混合是的
I guess mixes of loras when you create
你可以看到
your image yeah you can see how
它变得多么反差所以我认为
contrasty this is getting so I think
因为
because there's already a strong
詹妮弗安妮斯顿在
presence of Jennifer Aniston in the
实际的基本模型中已经有很强的存在即使低于 0.5
actual base model even going below 0.5
实际上可能足以得到
might actually be enough to get
像 0.3 这样的东西 在现有基础知识
something going like a 0.3 to get the
之上获得 Laura 的影响，而
influence of the Laura on top of the
不会受到
existing base knowledge without getting
太强的外国影响，
too strong an impact
foreign
所以这个应该产生更少的
so this one should produce much less
对比结果，这将更容易进行
contrasty results which would be easier
高档和升级，
to kind of upscale and upres
但
but
总的来说，
overall that's how it it works obviously
如果你的 主题已经不稳定
if your subject is not in stable
扩散你会得到
diffusion already you're gonna get a
很多你需要
much you're going to need a much higher
比现有模型更高的权重呃所以要
weight uh over the existing models so to
真正得到那个模型就像我
actually get that that model like I
可以向你展示的例如
could show you for example the other
我创建的另一个模型让我 去把
model I create let me go and bring a
它的副本放到
copy of that into
它需要的地方让我去
into where it needs to be let me go and
copy
这里复制蓝色 Laura
blue here Laura
所以让我拿 Cyndi Lauper 为例，
so let me bring Cyndi Lauper for example
这是我
which is the other one I did
剪下的另一个，现在让我们把它带到
cut this and now let's bring it into
我的稳定扩散中
my stable diffusion here
， 现在如果我在这里刷新如果我点击
and now if I refresh this here if I hit
刷新我们应该开始看到 uh Cyndi
refresh we should start to see uh Cyndi
Lauper 80s 所以如果我们要禁用这个
Lauper 80s so if we were to disable this
球如果我要使用
ball this and if I was to kind of use
Cyndi Lauper 1980s
the Cyndi Lauper 1980s
hits
Cindy law 非常适合
Cindy law perfect
我们生成
for us to generate
图片 什么会让 Cindy Lauper 变得非常糟糕，
a picture what would get a pretty bad
因为她
Cindy Lauper right because she's kind of
在稳定的
not very well known by the stable
扩散模型中不太为人所知，你可以看到
diffusion model you can kind of see that
她去过那里，就像她
she's been there like it's she she's
接受过培训一样，但
been trained but
它不是很好，
it's not very good images are pretty
rough
如果我们看的话，图像非常粗糙 它有点像它是
if we look at it like it's kind of there
她的旧版本
like it's an older version of of her
出现就像它有些更年轻
showing up like it's some are younger
但不是最好的但如果我
but not the best right but if I was to
现在去启用这个模型有
go and enable now this model with uh
一些重量让我们看看 0.7 这
some weight let's see 0.7 which is
通常是一个很好的比例 当
usually a good ratio when there's a
模型中有一些已知的
little bit of them of the model known
稳定积液影响时，
into stable effusion to influence and
现在我重新生成图像，您将
now I regenerate the image you're going
看到
to see a drastic difference in what the
输出已经存在的巨大差异，
output is going to be
您可以开始看到更多的
already you can start to see a lot more
存在
presence
of
Cindy
，你可以开始看到 1980 年代
and you can start to see much more
的 Cindy Lopper 的更多特征，
characteristics look for Cindy Lopper of
the 1980s
所以这是我制作的另一个模型，完全
so this is another model I made exactly
按照我给你展示的相同配方制作
following the same recipe I showed you
，现在你可以看到
for this one and now you can see the
一个
quite contrastic difference when a
人身体不适时的截然不同 以稳定
person is not well known to stable
扩散而闻名新火车 Dam 和 Laura 现在
diffusion a new train Dam and Laura now
你开始变得更生动
you start to get much more Vivid
就像那个人的输出所以
be like output of that person so
再次希望你喜欢这个希望它可以帮助
again hope you like this hope it helps
你了解如何训练和使用
you understand how to uh train and use a
Laura
与锦鲤 ISS 和汽车 1111 稳定
with koi ISS and auto 1111 stable
扩散
diffusion
呃网络用户界面
uh web UI
晚安
good night